{
    "id": "66cd7833342a4001b6816ac35fcdcf2c",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Put Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "ff75444da9a84153b456125279e508b6",
            "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Put",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "She puts ...................... a small amount every month towards her retirement.",
                    "description": "To put something by is to save an amount of money to use later. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "off",
                        "by",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The meeting has been put ...................... until Thursday.",
                    "description": "To put off is to postpone. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "off",
                        "up"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is just putting ...................... an act to win your sympathy.",
                    "description": "To put on an act is to fake and pretend. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "on",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I cannot put ............................... this heat.",
                    "description": "To put up with something is to tolerate it. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "up with",
                        "out with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The firemen worked hard to put .......................... the fire.",
                    "description": "To put out fire is to extinguish it. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "out",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Could you put me ............................. to the manager?",
                    "description": "To put x through to y is to connect x and y. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "through",
                        "into",
                        "up"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Don't forget to put the lights ........................ when you leave.",
                    "description": "To put lights out is to switch them off. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "off",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am sorry to have to put you ....................... this.",
                    "description": "To put somebody through something is to cause them to experience something. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "through",
                        "over"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You need good communication skills to be able to put your message ......................",
                    "description": "To put your message across is to communicate it. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "across",
                        "through"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "My professor has agreed to put a good word .................... for me.",
                    "description": "To put a word in for somebody is to recommend them. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "out",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "You had better put your coat ....................... before going out. It is very cold outside.",
                    "description": "To put on clothes is to wear them. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "over",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Everybody liked the suggestion put ........................... by Susie.",
                    "description": "To put forward a suggestion is to present it for other people's consideration. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "through",
                        "forward"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}